<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frequently Asked Questions on</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/</link><description>Recent content in Frequently Asked Questions on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to automatically show notes (popup) for a webpage?</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/notes_popup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/notes_popup/</guid><description>You can configure Page Notes to automatically show notes for a web page by changing &amp;ldquo;Automatically show notes pop-up&amp;rdquo; setting under &amp;lsquo;Advanced Settings&amp;rsquo;. There are 3 possible values of this setting:
Never Notes popup is not shown. Only for page-level notes (recommended): Notes popup is shown for the pages that have page-specific notes. For site-level notes as well: Notes popup is shown for all pages that have notes, either through page-level notes or site-level notes.</description></item><item><title>How to enable dark mode icon</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/dark_mode_icon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/dark_mode_icon/</guid><description>Extension will automatically switch to dark mode icons if you change OS settings to dark mode. You can change this behavior by changing the &amp;lsquo;Use dark mode icons&amp;rsquo; setting:
Auto (default) Automatically choose between dark and light mode icons based on the OS settings. Note that browser level theme change doesn&amp;rsquo;t trigger this change. Always Always use dark mode icons. Never Never use dark mode icons.</description></item><item><title>What Are Site-Level Notes?</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/site_level/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/site_level/</guid><description>Site-level notes are applied to all pages with the same hostname. For example, if you add a site-level note for github.com, that note will apply to all pages on github.com, including https://github.com/manugarg/pagenotes-issues, for example. If a page has both page-level and site-level notes, the page-level notes take priority.
You can mark a note as site-level when you edit it. You can also change the default setting through the options page.</description></item><item><title>Can I add a keyboard shortcut to open the notes</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/shortcut/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/shortcut/</guid><description>Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s a built-in feature in chrome. Visit chrome://extensions/shortcuts to create a shortcut for any extension. For example I use ^(Ctrl) + ⌘ (Cmd) + P (on Mac) for Page Notes.</description></item><item><title>Backup and Restore Notes</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/backup_restore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/backup_restore/</guid><description>You can back up your page notes from the options page. The backup is saved to disk in CSV format. You can also restore notes from a backup from the same, options, page.</description></item><item><title>Can I disable icon animation and badge</title><link>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/disable_icon_animation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:41:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pagenotes.manugarg.com/faq/disable_icon_animation/</guid><description>Yes, you can easily disable icon animation and &amp;lsquo;blue&amp;rsquo; badge from the options page.</description></item></channel></rss>